Mitch McConnell said that if Trump
pardoned and this was the original idea
Trump was going to Pardon Julian Assange
Ed Snowden and me and McConnell didn't
know me but he said if Trump pardoned
Assange and Snowden that he couldn't
control the Republican caucus in the
Senate and that they would probably vote
to convict him on the impeachment
charges so he dropped our Pardons and
Mitch McConnell I'd like to smack in his
Turtle face too but that's just me that
would be the final his final moments I
think he's like yeah I think so he's
pretty well dead as it is you know when
I was working on the hill we used to
make fun of him because he lives in this
townhouse that's literally four doors
down from the heart Senate Office
Building so he lives like literally 150
feet from his office and he used to take
a limo every morning the 150 feet and we
would boo him as he as he drove by like
what a loser